Art Collins Papers ARC.0001
Library and Archives
- Series I: Iggy Pop [RESTRICTED], 1985-2005, undated
  - Rollins, Henry catalog (2-13-61 Publications), 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Corn, Dr. Marvin (eyes), circa 1997 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Elektra royalty statement, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Southern, Terry obituary and Record World satirical salute to The Rolling Stones written by Southern, 1979, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - McCoy, Andy, documentary, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Anici, Greg, singer / songwriter, 1997 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Iggy updates, 1996 May (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Hustler photo, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Elle decoration, Iggy's apartment, 1997 April 4 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Shure / Iggy HW International distributed catalog UK, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Tower, Argentina, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - House of Blues "Summer of Love", 1997 March 10 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Byrds, Sony Legacy kit, 1996 March 22 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - "Lust For Life," Something For the Weekend CD, 1997 April 9 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Magnetic poetry, Esquire magazine, 1996 December 9 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Klausner, Julie Ana, Loyalty Press (sex thing), circa 1997 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Zebra Stripes / Richard Farrell, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Mahon, Maureen, Total Mayhem Productions, re: Core, 1997 September 5 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Voice of America radio, 1997 October 17 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Roman Empire / Alexandria Productions, 1997 September 18 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - VH1 100 Greatest Artists of Rock and Roll, 1997 September 25 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Turbov, Pam, HDCD Software Catalog, Volume One, 1997 October 14 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Rollins, Henry Publications royalty statements (2-13-61 Publications), 1997 September 25 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - "Lust For Life," History of Punk, Volume 2, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    Actual title, History of Rock, Volume 2
  - "Lust For Life," Best Indie LPs...Ever! (UK), 1997 September 24 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    Actual title: Best Indie Anthems...Ever!.
  - Made in Germany video use, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - "Lust For Life," student film, Saturday night Oil, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Shure microphone ads, 1997 September 4 (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Grimshaw, Gary, posters, 1988-1997 (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Popular History Company, Canadian TV release, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Rugrats movie contract, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Plotkin, Juliana, resume, 1997 February 28 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - MC5: A True Testimonial, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Gorman, Greg, Gia, television, 1997 May (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Pat Hearn Emergency Art Fund, 1997 March 13 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Baker, Martin, documentaries, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Bono / U2, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Dr. Chance, 2 songs / French, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Rynne, Frank, Islamic Diggers, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Nude and Rude report, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - German, Bill, 1996 October 23 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Virgin International plan, Nude and Rude, 1996 October (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Change of Heart (the band), 1997 April 3 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - "Lust For Life" DVD sampler (Western Europe), 1997 April (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Robbins, Irs, MJI Broadcasting, 1997 August 28 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Moviewatch, "Lust For Life", 1997 November 17 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Resumes, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Stooge-Staffel Music, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 1997 November (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Passengers, UK short film, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - "Passenger," Toyota ad, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Brockum merchandise, 1990-1997 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Kulpers, Dean / Ray Gun, 1997 September (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Dummett, Greg, Toronto Film Festival, Four Days, 1997 June (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Lyric book (Art), circa 1997 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - "China Girl," Covers (Japan), 1997 November 11 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Iggy / Larry letter, circa 1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - A&M royalty sheet, 1997 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Williamson, James, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Garcia, Jerry, Mick Rock stamps, 1997 October 2 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Hutchence, Michael, obituary, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Arnold, David, video thing, 1997 October (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Shaw, Greg, 11/97 Bomp!, 1997 November 2 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Incommunicado publishers, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Man on the Moon: The Loving Tongue / K. Laffey, 1996 December 4 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Royalty Records, Iggy tribute We Will Fall: The Iggy Pop Tribute, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Detroit Tigers, circa 1997 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Russia tour date, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - George, Lowell, tribute, 1997 Janauary 29 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Iggy / rider, 1997 August 19 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Raw Power label copy / Bug Music, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - JSR Merchandising, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Icon Magazine, 1996 November 19 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Virgin International promo, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Allen Ginsburg Trust, 1997 June 10 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - King Biscuit Flower Hour channel, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Ratcliffe, Jane, Hour, Detroit, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Red Hot Organization, 1997 April 7 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Rattlz CD, circa 1997 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Outer Reefs treatment, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Romanek, Mark / Contents magazine, 1997 July 23 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Pop, Iggy, Web page, circa 1997 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Cufaro, Chris, postcards, 1997 June 23 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Trainspotting II, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Technic ad request, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - "China Girl" / Feeling (ice cream), Chile request, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - "Gimme Danger," Whatever film, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - School of the Arts / Rochester, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Bowie, David, stock bonds, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Byatt, Noreen, thank you note, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Morcheeba group, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Razor and Tie catalog, Restless mail order catalog, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Los Angeles Without a Map script letter, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Hardy, Francoise, French standards, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Sexpod, Don Kaye, 1997 July 18 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Firecracker Alternative Book Awards, Rollins Publications, 1997 May 13 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Rock For Choice, August 1997, 1997July 30 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - South Bank Show / Susan Shaw, 1997 July 24 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Dwyer, Dr. Jim / NJ R, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Ashton, Liz, letter (and fan mail), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Burus, Bryant - 5th Annual "Burr-Fest", 1997 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - College Media Journal (CMJ) Music Festival brochure, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Spunk band kit, circa 1997 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Busacca, Larry, photographer, circa 1997 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Roar Tour premium CD, 1997 August 21 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - "China Girl," In Concert, 1996 October 16 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Progressive auto insurance, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Barr, Bryan, psycho letter, 1997 August 25 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Travis, auto insurance, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Poetry Project, 1997 September 29 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Utah Saints (Echo label), 1997 August 29 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Virgin statement, January to June, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Press clips, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 75-77)
  - Bug Music statement, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 78-79)
  - Rock, Mick, benefit, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Devil Deer, 1996-1998 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Girls travel [RESTRICTED], 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Family portrait and travel, 1997, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Photos and negatives are of a young Art Collins and his family.
  - "China Girl," Cupid, 1998 September (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - MTV BIOrhythm, "Winners and Losers", 1998 September (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - "Monster Man," French restaurant, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - "Lust For Life," Drew Carey Show, 1998 September 4 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Danny Clinch Photography, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Chelmsford, UK, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Slovakian UK date, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Call sheets, 1996, circa 1998 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - SLC Punk, 1998 April 19 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - MVO, US dates, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Itineraries, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Lava lamp information, circa 1998 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous (including French concerts), 1998 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Music Express limousine, 1998 August (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Call sheets, 1996, circa 1998 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Leeds UK, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Association Relative à la Télévision Européenne (ARTE) documentary, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Bizarre festival, 1998 August 12 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Skellefteaa Festival, Sweden, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Crossing Border Festival, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Lollipop Festival, 1998 May 11 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Esparrago Festival, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Portugal, May, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Rugrats final agreement, file copy, 1997 November 20 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Summer of Sam (Spike Lee movie), 1998 July 27 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - "Passenger," EMI Korea, 1998 July 23 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Warner / Chappell / Bug, Argentina, 1998 July 14 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Miami Vice buyout, 1998 July 10 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - "Louie, Louie," Kellogg's Spain, 1998 July 20 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - "Monster Man," TV ad, 1998 July 6 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - "Lust For Life," Best Car Video in the World... Ever!, 1998 July 16 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Fashion TV, Canada license, 1998 June 26 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - SLC Punk license, 1998 June 26 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - "Lust For Life," Top Gear Anthems, 1998 August (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - "China Girl," Disney, 1998 August 18 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - "Passenger," The Adventures of Sebastian Cole, 1998 August 20 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - MTV BIOrhythm, 1998 August 20 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - MTV Legends, 1998 August (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - MCPS education video, 1998 August (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Comte, Michael, book release, 1998 July 20 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - "Search and Destroy," APC clothing, 1998 August 25 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - MTV Influences, 1998 August 28 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - IBM renewal, 1998 August (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Call sheets, 1995-1999 (Box 5, Folder 48-52)
  - Pearl Jam tour contract, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 53-55)
  - Elvis tribute (and song licensing agreements), 1994, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Bug Music statement, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 57-58)
  - "Candy," Kilk films, 1999 September 22 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - "Passenger," Whipped film, 1999 September (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Bregovic, Gordon, songbook, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "Candy," The Complete 90s, 1999 October 13 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - "Success," Banana Republic, 1999 October (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - "Lust For Life," Best Anthems...Ever!, 1999 September 14 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - "Lust For Life," Millenium Movies, 1999 September (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - "Lust For Life," Mitsubishi TV, 1999 October 14 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - "Real Wild Child," German compilation, 1999 October 18 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - "Corruptor," Be Rock compilation, 1999 October 19 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - "Brick By Brick," Occy - The Rockymentary, 1999 October 14 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - "Lust For Life," Steinlager Beer, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You," Korean release, 1999 August 31 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - "Passenger"/ "Candy," Esso, 1999 August 16 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - "Nightclubbing," Oasis CD, 1999 August 30 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Eiffel Tower photographer (Lionel Guedj), 1999 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Photographer promo cards, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Dittmar, John, Pinnacle Entertainment, 1998 October 28 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Jacoves, Aaron D., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Burns, Andrew, 1998 December 29 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - "Passenger," Kasbah soundtrack, Spain, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - "Cry For Love", Time-Life Modern Rock, Volume 13, 1985-1989, 1999 November 30 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Avenue B record clubs - Virgin, 1999 December 7 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - "Lust For Life," Most Naked Bands - VH1 special, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - "Shakin' All Over," drug awareness, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - "Passenger," Digital Entertainment Network, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Motion picture, Orbiting Venus, "Search and Destroy", 1999 November 8 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - "Nightclubbing," Oasis sample, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Bregovic, Gordon, songbook CD, 1999 October (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - "Cold Metal," ESPN Olympics, 1999 December (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - "Real Wild Child," College Rock compilation, 1999 December 16 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Death In Vegas correspondence, 1999 September (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Hausen, Brent, President, MTV, 1993, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - William Morris sample contract [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Virgin Records, January-June, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - New album budget, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Weber, Bruce, Let's Get Lost, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - "Corruption" video shoot, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Sessions At W. 54th, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Avenue B press, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - New album travel, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Avenue B credits, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Avenue B adverts, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - A&R / Keith Wood, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Iggy home pictures, circa 1999 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Bomp! Records, 1997, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - New Millennium Communications, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Versace, Connie Flippello, 1999 October 22 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Jim travel, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Anthill t-shirts, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - International promo, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Best of Bowie DVD, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Bug Music statements, 1999 July-1999 September (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "Passenger," Doyle film (and other song licensing), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "Nightclubbing," Oasis sample, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "Real WIld Child," Rock Aus Dem Zwick Folge 1-10, 1999 November 3 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - "Lust For Life," Royal Carribean, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - It's Only Rock n' Roll, Children's Promise, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - All Access Radio, MTV broadcast, 1999 November (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "Miss Argentina," Humo's All 99 Goed, Benelux, 1999 October 29 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Europen mid-price Lust for Life / Idiot, 1999 October 18 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - "Living on the Edge of the Night" / Slow Motion, GSA countries, 1999 October 19 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - "Sixteen," La Puce French film, 1999 October 25 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - "Real Wild Child," Venezuela / Germany, 1999 May 10 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Recent licensing, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - "Passenger," Labbatt's Blue, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - "Lust For Life," EMI Scandinavia, 1999 May 10 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - "Wild America," Platinum Rock 90's, Australia / New Zealand, 1999 April 22 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - "China Girl," film, No Fun, Sex Pistols, 1999 May 13 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Metallic KO, V2 Records, sample use, 1999 April (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - "Lust For Life," Sofinco - French credit, 1999 April 30 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Soft Fruit, photo use, Australia, 1999 April 17 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Lock, Stock and Two Smoking Barrels, 1999 May 6 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - "Passenger," Virgin Sweden / Arista compilation, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Cioe, Crispin, Burnzy's Last Call, 1999 January 13 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Florida concert contracts, 1999 April (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - "Lust For Life," This is Cult Fiction, 1999 March 24 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - "Real Wild Child," Mexico CD, 1999 March 24 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - "Technowledgy," BIOrhythm: Missy Elliot, 1999 March 23 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Continental, Gig Trigger 4 / 1999, 1999 March 8 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Static Records, Pop O.D. - The Songs of Iggy Pop CD, circa 1999 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - "Search and Destroy," Detroit Rock City, 1999 April 13 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - "Nightclubbing," Ange (French film), 1999 April 15 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - "Passenger," Sony Music (Norway), 1999 May 10 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - "Real Wild Child," Rock of the Century, 1999 April 30 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - "Passenger," Rock the Vote, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - "Lust For Life," Nokia Singapore, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - "Living on the Edge of the Night," 90's Collection, 1999 September 27 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - "Search and Destroy," When Brenden Met Teddy, Eric film, 1999 September 14 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - "Success," Banana Republic; "Nightclubbing," Oasis sample, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - "Living on the Edge of the Night," Wonderful 80's, 1999 October 5 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - "Lust For Life," FIFA 2000 The Album, GSA release, 1999 October 5 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - "Lust For Life," Motivaction CD-ROM, 1999 July 15 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - "Passenger," Virgin 25 Years, 1999 July 22 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - "Real Wild Child," Best Beer Drinking Songs Ever, New Zealand, 1999 July 27 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - "Girls of NY," French perfume, 1999 September (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - "Lust For Life," Born to Be Wild, Virgin UK, 1999 February 3 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - VH1 Behind the Music, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - "Kill City," charity sampler, 1999 June 25 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - "Lust For Life," Power List -- Scotland Angel synopsis, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - "Lust For Life," Transworld gift CD, 1999 April 19 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - "Lust For Life," La Femme Nakita, 1999 April (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - "Candy," Benelux, Top 10 Rock Hits, 1999 April 9 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - "Lust For Life," Spiked! The Punk Years, Canada CD, 1999 April 9 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - "Louie, Louie," Extreme Surf, Sweden, 1999 April 9 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - "Highway Song," Motor City Music, Volume 2, Baltic states CD, 1999 April 9 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - "Pumpin' For Jill," Sweden, 1999 February 22 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - "Real Wild Child," Germany, Austria, Swiss, 1999 February 23 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - "Funtime," VH1 Legends: David Bowie, 1999 January 21 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - "Passenger," Barney Simon CD, 1999 September 3 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - "Passenger," DSB Denmark, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - "No Fun," Sex Pistols movie Filth and the Fury, 1999 October 6 (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Pizza Hunt, "Passenger" / "Corruption", 1999 November 16 (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - "Real Wild Child," Rock and Pop Moods, Netherlands, 1999 November 5 (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - "Orbiting Venus," Master charge, Bug Music, 1999 October 28 (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - "Real Wild Child," Rock and Pop Classics, Vol. 15, 1999 November 17 (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - Toyota UK, "Passenger," 2000 option, 1999 November 9 (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - "Lust For Life," Best of the 70's, Europe release, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 70)
  - "Real Wild Child," A&M Portugal, 1999 June 21 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Bust Magazine reprint request, 1999 January 20 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - "Real Wild Child," A&M Australia, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - "Technowledgy," BIOrhythm: Missy Elliot, 1999 February 19 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - "China Girl," Late Lunch, EMI UK, 1999 February 22 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - "Pumpin' For Jill" commercial, 1999 February (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - "Lust For Life," Honda Civic, 1999 February 22 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Bug Music, Stooges compositions, Warner, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Amen group, John Reese Management, 1999 February 22 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Nude and Rude mid-price campaign, 1999 February 22 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Romanek, Mark, book, "Beside You" pictures, 1999 February 18 (Box 7, Folder 81)
  - Motorhead tribute CD, 1998 December 16 (Box 7, Folder 82)
  - Mark Seliger Photography, 1999 January 20 (Box 7, Folder 83)
  - Yanky Panky, UK show, 1999 February 16 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - "I Wanna Live," Virgin, Chevy Camaro, 1999 March 11 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - "Real Wild Child" compilation, Portugal, 1999 March 17 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - "Lust For Life," Virgin, Ally McBeal Special, 1999 March (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - "Search and Destory," Cameron Crowe film, DreamWorks, 1999 March 16 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - Goran Bregovic Songbook, 1999 June 3 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - "Lust For Life," Procter and Gamble, 1999 June 9 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - "Real Wild Child," A&M Australia, 1999 June 11 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - "Passenger," LaBatt's Blue, 1999 June (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - Bicentennial Man, Virgin / Bug Music, "Lust For Life", 1999 June (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - "Real Wild Child," Time-Life Music, 1999 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - "Passenger" / "I Got a Right," Digital Entertainment Network, 1999 June 11 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - "Shake Appeal," All Cheerleaders Die, 1999 February 12 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - "I Wanna Live," Ooh La La, Bug Music and other song licensing, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Trivial Pursuit, 1999 March 10 (Box 7, Folder 98)
  - High Fidelity, movie, MVO, 1999 May 1999 (Box 7, Folder 99)
  - HBO Reverb, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 100)
  - ? and The Mysterians, 1999 April 28 (Box 7, Folder 101)
  - "Real Wild Child," Polygram Netherlands, Time-Life Vol. 15, 1999 June 29 (Box 7, Folder 102)
  - "I Wanna Be Your Dog," Rock Candy / Bug Music, 1999 June 17 (Box 7, Folder 103)
  - "Lust For Life," EMI Korea, 1999 June 22 (Box 7, Folder 104)
  - Save the Children Millennium Project gig, 1999 June 15 (Box 7, Folder 105)
  - Versace men's show, Milan, January 1999, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 106)
  - Virgin statements, June-December (and exclusive Avenue B performance tickets), 1999 (Box 7, Folder 107)
  - "I'll Be Seeing You," 20th Century Lullabies, 1999 September 10 (Box 7, Folder 108)
  - Canal+ Belgium taping, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 109)
  - MTV 1999 Euro Awards letters, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 110)
  - Nightclubbing in Paris, Canal+ special, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 111)
  - Sigworth, Sig, memos, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 112)
  - Anthill merchandising, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 113)
  - Thousand Mile Incorporated (TMI) / Grumble Corporation income, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 114)
  - Grumble Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1999 (Box 7, Folder 115)
  - BMI royalty information, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 116)
  - Tosches, Nick, letter, 1999 October 31 (Box 7, Folder 117)
  - Principle Management, Dublin, Ireland, 1998 November 19 (Box 7, Folder 118)
  - U.S. promo, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 119)
  - Solo Agency, Fall offers, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 120-121)
  - Call sheets and Avenue B European Tour book, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 122-124)
  - Outstanding 1999 promo requests (Box 7, Folder 125)
  - V98 Festival photographer lawsuit, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 126)
  - MTV European awards, 1999 November 17 (Box 7, Folder 127)
  - Britannica.com, Deutsch advertising, 1999 August (Box 7, Folder 128)
  - Avenue B international marketing plan, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 129)
  - Set list, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 130)
  - Virgin catalog contract (and song licensing), 1994-1995, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 131)
  - Home to Rent Space Goofs, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 132)
  - Jewel Box Platinum, Inc., Trainspotting CD, 1997 June (Box 7, Folder 133)
  - Virgin / Gaumont battle, 1996, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 134)
  - Royalty contracts (and Bug Music statement), 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 135)
  - Snow Day movie, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1999 Revenge royalties (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "Kiss My Blood" video and Revenge royalties, 1991-1992, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Royalty statements, July-December, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Royalty statements, January-March, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - MVO offers, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Grumble Corporation [RESTRICTED], 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 7-8)
  - Revenge / MCA Records, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Revenge royalties, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Was, Don, deal, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Revenge contract, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Carroll, Rosemary, Virgin license, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)